It was like, how did
you know it was me?
IT WAS LIKE, HOW
DID YOU KNOW
It was like, how did
you know it was me?
It was like, I told
you I found you, and
put you over. A report
of police misconduct
sparks a criminal
investigation,
revealing not only a
disturbing abuse of
automated license
plate recognition
systems, but just how
far a Florida deputy
was willing to go to
get what he wanted.
It's early March,
2026, and Deputy Lamar
Roman has been pulled
off patrol and brought
to the Monroe County
Sheriff's Office
headquarters.
Supervisors take his
duty belt and his
firearms before
sitting down for a
meeting that's
anything but routine.
Okay, what do you
think was it?